ximage.me 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy - Ximage

Privacy Policy:

Ximage (“Ximage”) operates [Ximage.me](https://ximage.me/) and may operate other websites. It is Ximage’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites.  
Website Visitors

Like most website operators, Ximage collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Ximage’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Ximage’s visitors use its website. From time to time, Ximage may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

Ximage also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on Ximage.me blogs/sites. Ximage only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below, except that commenter IP addresses and email addresses are visible and disclosed to the administrators of the blog/site where the comment was left.  
Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

**We Respect you email related Privacy!!!**  
Ximage will Save Subscriber IP Save IP address and time of new subscribers to comply with other country regulations! In some countries it’s required to save the IP address and the sign up time for legal reasons.  
Ximage honors and supports the Do Not Track Respect users “Do Not Track” option on site and we do not track, unless our third party advertisement collects any information we cant control their privacy settings, how ever our server and site is setup to honor and fully function with the Do Not Track option in your browser.  
If subscribed to our site it will respect users option for not getting tracked. Read more above.  
Single-Opt-Out Subscribers instantly signed out after clicking the unsubscribe link in mails

Certain visitors to Ximage’s websites choose to interact with Ximage in ways that require Ximage to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Ximage gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up at Ximage.me to provide a username and email address. Those who engage in transactions with Ximage are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, Ximage collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with Ximage. Ximage does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.  
Aggregated Statistics

Ximage may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. Ximage may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Ximage does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.  
Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information.

**Acknowledgement**  
By accessing and viewing this site, you acknowledge that you have read and understood these Legal [Terms of Service](https://ximage.me/terms-of-service/). These terms can be modified by us at any time without notice.  
Automatic Logging  
For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server automatically recognizes the consumer’s domain name and IP address to diagnose problems with our server and help identify you for on-line voting.  
Cookies  
We use cookies to store visitors preferences, record session information, target ads, and help identify you for on-line voting.  
Use of Information  
Information collected by the server through cookies and other means will not be shared with anyone for any purpose. The sole purpose of it is to improve the site’s operations and content.  
External Links  
This site contains links to other sites. Ximage.me is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites.  
Contacts  
If you have any questions or concerns regarding the privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site feel free to contact us at on our [contact page](https://ximage.me/dmca/) and fill out the form for prompt response.

Ximage discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Ximage’s behalf or to provide services available at Ximage’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Ximage’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Ximage will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Ximage discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when Ximage believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Ximage, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an Ximage website and have supplied your email address, Ximage may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Ximage and our products. If you send us a request (for example via email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Ximage takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.  
Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Ximage uses cookies to help Ximage identify and track visitors, their usage of Ximage website, and their website access preferences. Ximage visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Ximage’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of Ximage’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.  
Business Transfers

If Ximage, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Ximage goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Ximage may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.  
Ads

Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Ximage and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.  
Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Ximage may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Ximage’s sole discretion. Ximage encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. If you have a Ximage.me account, you might also receive an alert informing you of these changes. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

Privacy Policy updated: 02/27/2016
